Destiny. Fate. Dreams.
These unstoppable ideals are
held deep in the heart of man.
As long as there are people
who seek freedom in this life,
these things shall not
vanish from the earth.
People tell me my head's in the clouds.
I don't care what they say
because I'm dreaming of you!
You are the treasure I found.
So bright, so bold, it's so elusive?
It's hard to look away.
Even though it's blinding me!
There are no words to
describe how I feel inside.
I'm really, really stuck on you!
I have to follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem.
And I won't stop till I
get there, you will see!
You're all I need to have
the strength to believe.
Believe in what I do!
I'm gonna follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem.
I'm gonna share them
with you, a love so true.
You're all I want,
together we can move on.
We live how we want to.
There is no limit to us!
We have the power of love.
We don't want to live ordinary life.
We have a chance to live in paradise.
We live in one another.
Guys, listen up.
I will go to Elbath someday.
To the village of warriors!
Yeah, great!
Jaggy giants!
Jaggy giants! Elbath! Elbath!
Everyone is huge!
They're so huge!
Because they're giants!
Gi-gi-giants!
Everybody's huge!
Where do they get so much
energy? Everybody's huge!
Wow, after everything that's
happened here, I'm exhausted.
Um, Vivi, could you
watch this for me? Sure.
You're on your way.
Soon you'll return to Alabasta. Well,
my rosy outlook is assuming we can make it
there safely and without
any more surprises.
Yes, I must return.
It's my obligation.
I am the person everyone in
the kingdom is counting on.
Believe me when I say it is the
only way to save the kingdom.
It is true that your father no
longer has sway with the people.
Our only hope of stopping this uprising
is for you to tell them the truth.
This is the only action that can save us.
You have to understand that
your survival is paramount.
You must live, even if it
means sacrificing others.
Whether by grace or betrayal,
live on, no matter what.
Sometimes, it's harder
to live than to die.
I will return home, alive.
You'll get home but
there's no need to push
yourself so hard you've
got me here you go try.
These sweets they'll
help you relax I've made
some delicious tarts and
your choice of coffee
or tea thank
you yours
are in the kitchen now
six oh
three six oh
four six oh five six six?
Damn it all,
if I only got to cut that wax, I
wouldn't have left anyone hanging there.
I'm so weak.
If I'm going to get stronger,
I need to be able to slice through
stuff like that from any stance.
Mr.
2, Bond Clay, the swanda
is ready to set sail.
Okay, okay, I heard you. Chouchou.
Do you have to scream?
Honestly, somebody give me one good
reason why I should be the one to do this.
Mr.
3 is a piece of garbage.
Go toss him out yourselves.
That's impossible.
We wouldn't even stand
a chance against him.
But you have to help.
Those were the boss's orders.
Un, deux, trois.
What's four again? Anybody?
That zero.
So much trouble.
Evie, I'm sorry, but I...
I need to rest.
I understand.
Nami, don't worry.
Everything's under control.
I'll keep an eye on her.
Course,
you're
burning up.
Hey, everyone, come quick!
What's wrong?
Baby, are you okay?
Nami has an awful
What?
Nami's sick?
It's most likely the climate.
It's quite normal.
See?
Sailors in the Grand Line are used to the
strange weather and can become quite ill.
There are countless stories of tough,
notorious pirates who suddenly died.
Their immune systems were attacked
and ravaged by colds and fevers.
Ignoring the symptoms can make
even the slightest cold deadly.
Mommy!
Is there anyone aboard this ship with even
the slightest amount
of medical experience?
Well, when you're sick, eating
lots of meat always helps.
Right, Sanji?
Meat is protein, and that does give
the body energy to operate properly.
I can cook some foods that'll boost
your energy, but there's no guarantees.
I'm not a doctor.
Besides, if my cooking made that big
a difference, she'd never get sick.
I put a hundred times more care into
preparing her meals than I do for you losers.
I serve Nami fresh meats and
vegetables to ensure a balanced diet.
Anything that's rotten or
moldy goes to you. Jerk!
Oh well, still tastes good to me.
My point is that as long
as I'm this ship's cook,
nobody's going to feed Nami
better in terms of nutrition.
I can do anything in the kitchen.
Still, I do know that there are specific
foods for different kinds of illnesses.
But I can't make that call.
She needs to be diagnosed by a doctor
who'll tell us how to help her.
Just feed her everything that we've got.
Oh, shut up.
She doesn't have the energy to eat.
She's sick.
One hundred more.
No, this isn't good.
There's bound to be doctors and nurses
in Alabasta that can help, right?
How much longer till we get there, Vivi?
I don't know.
At least a week, and that's too long.
Okay, so she's sick.
Maybe we're overreacting.
I don't know.
I've never been this sick. Morons!
Have you all lost your minds?
This is serious!
She shouldn't have such a high fever
unless her body's fighting an infection.
This is bad.
Whatever's wrong, it's
possibly life-threatening.
You mean Nabi's gonna die!
Your screams aren't helping!
We have to find a doctor to
help Nabi before she dies!
Okay, everyone just calm down.
You're only going to make her feel worse.
Listen.
I'm fine.
Nami?
Yay!
She's cute! Shut up!
Go to my desk.
Open the second drawer.
There's a newspaper in the bottom.
No change in our course.
No.
That's not possible.
Huh? What's up? Something wrong?
Is it about Alabasta? Tell us.
According to this article, 300,000 royal
soldiers have defected to the resistance.
Until now,
we've been embroiled
in a cold war with 600
,000 royal soldiers
against 400,000 rebels.
With this, the balance has shifted.
The uprising in Alabasta
will seriously escalate now.
Things will get ugly.
That paper you're looking
at is three days old
I'm sorry.
I didn't say something earlier.
We can't change our speed.
So I didn't want to
worry you There's nothing
anyone can do right now
You understand Luffy?
Things are bad and
they're beyond our control
it sunk in better than I'd hope Nami Look,
you need to see a doctor right away.
I'm fine.
The thermometer is broken I mean come
on nobody gets a temperature of 104.
It's probably just a mild
case of sunstroke There's
nothing a doctor can do
for me that time won't.
Besides, we don't have
time to hunt for one.
We need to head straight
for Alabasta, right?
I appreciate the concern. Thank you.
Huh.
She sure recovered fast.
No, she's faking.
Now that this conflict has escalated,
more blood will be shed
throughout the kingdom.
We're at war.
If I don't put a stop to this insanity,
the entire kingdom of
Alabasta will be doomed.
Crocodile will move in and seize control.
You're trying to get me home
safely, but there's no time.
I need to get home as quickly as possible.
If I don't make it back in time,
a million innocent citizens will
give their lives needlessly.
There's a million people there? Wow!
What a horrible burden you
have to carry. I'm sorry.
Saru, what the hell have you
been watching all this time?
What are you talking about?
We've been going straight
ahead as you ordered.
Oh yeah, straight at a right angle.
Look at the eternal pose.
It doesn't lie.
I don't need to look at it.
I've been using that big
cloud over there as my guide.
You moron!
Clouds move and change shape constantly!
Ow!
Jeez, my head's killing me.
So leave them navigating
to me and go to bed.
I wish that I could, but I'm here
because I can't trust you with this.
The air has changed. What do you mean?
Weather's been nice like this all day.
Never mind.
Just get the others.
Hey!
Get your butts out here!
Right now!
What do you want?
You know, I find it hard to get
motivated when you're giving the orders.
Shut up and get moving.
Take the seat and catch
the port side wind.
Nami, what's up?
It's a perfect day.
The sun is shining.
The waves are quiet.
The wind.
Wind?
There's a powerful wind.
It's heading right this way. I think...
Luffy?
Your head's on fire!
You gotta stay in bed and
we need to get you a doctor!
Maybe you should mind your own business.
This is my normal temperature.
Now quit being so stupid
and pull the damn ropes.
Nami,
I know you're acting brave for
Vivi, but if you keep pushing,
your body won't have a chance to heal.
Aw.
I told you guys I'm fine. Let it go.
Whoa, hey, take it easy.
Not another word, damn it.
Hurry and move the ship.
All right, we're on it.
That ain't.
Chouchou, something I don't know, but
something's headed this way and soon.
I need to get home before time runs out.
I have to ask you all a favor.
As a passenger on your ship, it's not my
place to ask this, but I have no choice.
My homeland is in jeopardy
of being destroyed,
so I would really appreciate it
if we could move even faster.
Every minute I'm out here puts more of my
people in danger of losing their lives.
We need to head for
Alabasta at full speed.
Of course, we will just like we promised.
Then it's settled.
Let's find an island with
a doctor on it right away.
First things first, we need to
hurry and get Nami healthy again.
Then we head for Alabasta.
After all, we need her at the
helm to move at top speed.
Right?
No one makes this ship move like Nami.
Princess, hold on.
Won't finding a doctor for Nami take time
the citizens of Alabasta just don't have?
That's right.
So the sooner we get Nami a doctor,
the sooner we can get to Alabasta.
Those are wise words, Vivi.
You're beautiful and brilliant.
The girl's got guts.
Thank you, Vivi.
Don't overexert yourself, Nami.
I'm...
I'm sorry.
I may need to, like... Nami!
What the hell is that?!
It's a cyclone!
It's huge!
Wait!
That's the same path we were headed on!
Phoebe's right!
That's the exact same direction!
It would've been a direct hit
if we kept going straight!
We'd be dead right now!
See that?
Way too close!
We barely missed it!
Incredible.
Cyclones in the Grand Line are
said to be impossible to predict.
But somehow Nami did.
However she does it,
it's obvious her technique isn't
based on any conventional method.
It's as if she's detecting
the weather with her body.
It's beyond reason. A miracle.
Alright!
What are we waiting here for?
Let's find Nami a doctor!
Yeah!
Oh, what are we going to do, Vivi?
Nami's fever won't go down!
Hey, guys, stop!
That behavior isn't helping!
See any doctors yet?
Lupi, you can't be serious.
Uh hey guys what do you think about people
standing on water what
do i think it's possible?
What kind of question
is that it's impossible
of course yeah well then
what's that what's what?
Say what?
Hello, sure it's chilly today.
Yeah, it is chilly today.
Definitely, it's very chilling.
In fact, I would even say it's freezing.
Really?
Increase buoyancy! Right!
What is that thing? A watermelon?
Why are we shaking?
Hold the rudder steady!
If anything happens to Nami, I'll
hold every one of you responsible!
What the hell is that?
Is that a ship?
Oh, crap!
It's a pirate ship!
It's huge!
Great.
Just when we needed to hurry.
What's the matter?
Don't tell me our underwater raid
ship, the Tin Tyrant, surprised you!
Phoebe, you're in charge. All right.
Hey, what's going on?
So, what's going on?
Well, we're under attack
and it's still snowing.
Well yeah the guns pointing
at my face kind of gave
that one away what next you
all consider Yourself a band
of pirates that's amusing
i only count for you sort
of strange that your group
would have so few members.
Kid, it's just weird.
What kind of guy likes to eat knives? Ah!
My gums are bleeding just watching!
All right, I'll keep this simple.
See, my men here and I wish
to travel to Drum Kingdom.
You wouldn't happen to have an
eternal pose or a Log Pose, would you?
Nope, can't help.
Sorry, but I've never even
heard of this Drum Kingdom.
Well, now that we have that all settled,
would you guys just leave already?
We're in a hurry, and we don't
have time to deal with all this.
You'll never enjoy life if
you're always in a rush.
But if you have neither
pose, what can be done?
I suppose I'll have to settle
for your treasure on this ship.
First things first.
I'm feeling a bit hungry.
He's a shippity monster!
Hey, our ship isn't your lunch! Be quiet!
Wapol doesn't like to be
disturbed while he's eating!
Shut up!
Damn pirate, we're under attack!
Shoot him!
Now things are finally
starting to get interesting.
Perfect.
This is more like it. Stop it!
Can't we discuss this?
They took it upon themselves
to start this. What fools!
They got a death wish?
Gunfire!
Karoo, stay here and watch Nami.
I'll be right back.
You shouldn't take on
anything you can't handle.
Reception!
Oh, Bart, no bite.
Hey, um, Wapol, we need help.
You still eat it!
This ship doesn't taste
half bad. Hey, you!
You fool!
You're no master Wapol.
Now you'll be eaten by the
power of the Munch Munch.
Let me know!
What's this?
Oh, hey there, Vivi.
Everything okay with Nami?
I'd prefer someone less chewy.
I said...
Waffle?
This is bad.
He sent Waffle flying out into the ocean.
Bad? It's worse. It's a disaster.
Waffle's gonna drown.
He can't swim.
Recall the troops.
There's no time to waste.
We have to rescue him before
he sinks to the bottom!
Go, go, go!
This is far from over! You'll pay!
I promise you'll pay!
You're dead, you brat!
You'd better hope Waffle doesn't die!
Or it's your blood we'll spill!
Remember that!
We'll get you for this!
Wow, crazy.
Those guys are really upset.
What were they calling that
old garbage can, Waffle?
Who cares about what his name was?
Don't worry about it.
The guy's obviously a moron.
Best to just forget about him.
I know him.
But from where?
I know.
Dows her in water.
That'll fix her.
You idiot!
This isn't good.
The sun's about to set
and she's still the same.
Yeah, right.
Maybe it would be best if
we drop anchor somewhere.
We can't navigate at night anyway
without the help of Nami's instructions.
That's true.
It sure is a cold one.
Almost a full moon.
Crap, I fell asleep.
You're up early.
Can't just sit around doing nothing.
We've got to find a way out of
this jam as quick as possible.
You're right.
That's a good point.
Say, Usa, does this area
seem unusually calm and cold?
Yeah, now that you
mention it, it sure does.
And to be honest, it's freaking me out.
The Grand Line just
keeps getting stranger.
That's not necessarily true.
Huh?
Maybe there's an island nearby.
Hey, Sanji, will you check the
horizon for any sign of land?
Sure thing.
There's a Winter Island
somewhere nearby, I think.
Winter Island?
Scattered within the Grand Line,
there are four basic types of islands
made distinct by their varying climates.
You've got Summer Islands, Spring Islands,
Autumn Islands, and of
course Winter Islands.
Each one has its own
four independent seasons.
When traveling on the Grand Line,
there are at least 16 different types of
weather patterns you must
be prepared to endure,
ranging from Summer Island, Summer,
all the way to Winter Island,
Winter, and everything in between.
There can always be exceptions to this,
and you could even encounter unknown
climates at any given moment.
I think I get it.
The Grand Line has all these different
islands, one after the other.
And that's the reason why the seas between
them have such crazy unstable
weather patterns. Correct.
And the closer you get to an island,
the calmer the sea is around you.
Which is why I asked Sanji
to start looking for land.
That's it.
I see it.
Huh?
Island dead ahead!
Are you serious?
Oh, an island!
We found an island!
Hey, Nami, did you hear that?
This means we can get
you to a real doctor.
He'll fix you up. Wake up.
Wake up.
Wake up. Wake up.
Just go, Luke.
I've got her covered.
There it is!
Nami's saved!
All right, it's snow.
A snow island. Whoa.
Luffy, wait.
Just so there's no
misunderstanding between us.
We're stopping to find Nami a doctor.
We're not here to have an adventure.
Are we clear?
I love snow.
It's so white. It's no use. He's gone.
Hold on.
You sure this is a good idea?
There could be snow monsters.
Besides, we don't even know if
there's people there or not.
Oh, no.
I'm having a relapse if I
don't go to the island disease.
Ah, snow.
It's so white and beautiful.
Guess I'll get ready for the inevitable.
Ah, I'm so happy!
Look at the snow!
Look at the mountains.
They're unlike anything I've ever seen.
Say, Luffy, aren't you
cold dressed like that?
It's ten degrees below freezing out here.
That's when bears get ready to hibernate.
Huh?
Oh, boy. Cold!
You just figured that out!
It's a stream of melted snow.
This may provide a good spot to disembark.
Okay guys, Dr.
Search, who wants in?
Guess we gotta find people here first.
I'm in! Me too!
Ah, go have fun!
That's far enough, pirates!
People!
Well, that was easy.
Yeah, nice.
But they don't seem too friendly.
I'll only say this once.
Your kind is not welcome here.
Leave immediately.
We only came here to find a doctor.
We have someone who's sick.
You'll have to do better than that.
We won't fight for that old trip.
This is our island.
We won't let any filthy pirates land here.
Raise anchor and leave now or we'll
blow you and your ship out of the water.
That's great We barely said
hello, and they already hate us?
Big mistake!